valuecommerce.com 2016-06-30

# Privacy Policy | ValueCommerce Co., Ltd.

## Privacy Policy

ValueCommerce Co., Ltd. (hereinafter, the “Company”) is a company that provides comprehensive consulting services with a focus on affiliate marketing services, including search engine marketing services. As a result, there are many instances where we deal with a range of information about our advertisers and partners, and we consider it to be our very important social responsibility to acknowledge the importance of this information and to handle the information itself in an appropriate manner.

Regarding the protection of personal information that may allow the identification of a private individual, we hereby declare that we will specify, implement and maintain the following items:

  1. In acquiring personal information, the Company will specify the purpose of its use as much as possible, and will acquire personal information only to the extent required to achieve this purpose.
  2. If personal information is to be acquired directly from the individual in writing, the Company will provide the Company name, the name and the contact address of the Personal Information Protection Administrator, and the purpose of use, and will acquire the personal information only to the extent required.
  3. The use of personal information will be limited to the extent of the consent to the purpose of use provided by the individual. Furthermore, the Company will establish procedures for implementing the necessary measures to prevent its use outside the purpose.
  4. The Company will manage the personal information on hand accurately and in accordance with the latest methods, in keeping with the purpose of use, only to the extent necessary, and will establish reasonable safety measures for protection against leaks, losses or damage to the personal information in order to prevent and correct them.
  5. The Company will manage the personal information appropriately and does not disclose and provide personal information to third parties without consent of the individual.
  6. When the Company is to outsource the processing of personal information, the appropriate management will be undertaken by putting in place contractual obligations against leaks or the provision of the information to third parties.
  7. Any complaints or consultations regarding the protection of personal information can be addressed by contacting the Company’s inquiry section.
  8. The Company will comply with the laws and guidelines set forth by the government and other regulations that apply to the protection of personal information.
  9. The Company will establish a management system regarding the protection of personal information, and will review it regularly and make continuous improvements.

Established: November 1, 2011  
Latest revision: June 16, 2016  
ValueCommerce Co., Ltd.  
Jin Kagawa, Representative Director,  
President and CEO

### Inquiry section for matters concerning the protection of personal information

Please contact the following for any complaints, consultations, inquiries about disclosure and other matters in person, regarding the handling of personal information and the personal information protection management system. A prompt response will be provided appropriately.

Address:  
Personal Information Protection Administrator,   
ValueCommerce Co., Ltd.  
Ark Hills South Tower  
1-4-5 Roppongi, Minato-ku, Tokyo

### The purpose of use of personal information held by the Company and personal information subject to disclosure

#### 1\. Name of operator handling personal information

Personal Information Protection Administrator,  
ValueCommerce Co., Ltd.

#### 2\. Matters concerning the purpose of use of “personal Information held by the Company”

The purpose of use of “personal information held by the Company” will be as follows:

##### 1\. Personal information of those applying for positions in the Company during the recruitment screening (CV, etc.)

Disclosed

To be used in the recruitment screening process of the individual. The personal information of CV, etc. for those who are not recruited will be disposed of by the Company at its responsibility.

##### 2\. Personal information of Company employees considered necessary for operations at the Company (CV, etc.)

Disclosed

To be used to process the general affairs and accounting requirements of the individual. When the information is obtained, the purpose of its use will be clearly indicated before it is obtained, and it will be used only to the extent of this purpose.  
The personal information of retired employees will either be returned to the individual or disposed of by the Company at its responsibility.

##### 3\. Advertiser information (Affiliate)

Disclosed

To be used for the following services for the advertisers:

  * 1) Sending information materials by e-mail
  * 2) Telephone communication concerning requests for sales visits, etc.
  * 3) Sales visits *around the time of prior review, depending on the circumstances
  * 4) Responses to inquiries (e-mail, telephone)
  * 5) Legal compliance, credit check
  * 6) Reporting e-mail containing the results of prior review
  * 7) Sending information materials through the post
  * 8) Reissuing passwords
  * 9) E-mail magazine distribution
  * 10) Information about campaigns and questionnaires
  * 11) Disclosure of information for communication between the parties in the case of a breach of rules or contract

##### 4\. Publisher information (Affiliate)

Disclosed

To be used for the following services for the publishers:

  * 1) Review of Affiliates
  * 2) Reporting and communicating review results, etc.
  * 3) Reissuing passwords
  * 4) Communication concerning requests for sales visits, etc.
  * 5) Responses to inquiries (e-mail, telephone)
  * 6) Identifying individuals
  * 7) E-mail magazine distribution
  * 8) Information about campaigns and questionnaires
  * 9) Control screen log-in authentication
  * 10) Indicating the site name, site URL, site content, name of person in charge of contract (company name in the case of company registration) and average daily number of accesses to the EC site operator or advertising agency appointed by the EC site operator when an application for affiliation for advertisement carriage is made
  * 11) Dispatch of mail, merchandise, etc.
  * 12) Disclosure of information for communication between the parties in the case of a breach of rules or contract
  * 13) Payment of compensation

##### 5\. Advertiser information (Storematch)

Disclosed

To be used for the following services for the advertisers:

  * 1) Review of site
  * 2) Communicating and reporting review results, etc. (notice e-mail)
  * 3) Reissuing passwords when lost
  * 4) Identifying individuals
  * 5) Sending materials by e-mail
  * 6) Telephone communication concerning requests for sales visits, etc.
  * 7) E-mail magazine distribution
  * 8) Various settings to carry advertisements
  * 9) Information about sales promotion

##### 6\. Visitor log book completed as an entrance procedure by visitors to the Company (visitor history)

Disclosed

To be used to ensure the security of the Company (entry and exit control)

##### 7\. Personal information of individuals who have made inquiries via the Company’s website (inquiry history)

Disclosed

To be used to confirm and respond to the content of the inquiry

##### 8\. App developer information (Applis)

Disclosed

To be used for the following services for app developers:

  * 1) Sending information materials by e-mail
  * 2) Reporting and communicating review results, etc.
  * 3) Reissuing passwords
  * 4) Identifying individuals
  * 5) E-mail magazine distribution
  * 6) Control screen log-in authentication
  * 7) Indicating the app name, icon, heading, introduction, name of person in charge of contract (company name in the case of company registration), supported OS, market URL, URL for the original landing page, version, category, size, promotional text, tag, price, social count and registration rate to media in response to app information search. If you do not want your real name indicated as the person in charge of contracts, please enter a handle instead in the relevant field.
  * 8) Disclosure of information for communication between the parties in the case of a breach of rules or contract

##### 9\. Media (Applis)

Disclosed

To be used for the following services for the media:

  * 1) Sending information materials by e-mail
  * 2) Telephone communication concerning requests for sales visits, etc.
  * 3) Sales visits *around the time of prior review, depending on the circumstances
  * 4) Responses to inquiries (e-mail, telephone)
  * 5) Reissuing passwords
  * 6) Identifying individuals
  * 7) E-mail magazine distribution
  * 8) Control screen log-in authentication
  * 9) Indicating the name of the media site, company name and URL to app developers in response to a registered media search
  * 10) Sending information materials through the post

##### 10\. Value Point Club

Disclosed

To be used for the following services:

  * 1) Communicating and reporting member registration and others
  * 2) Reissuing passwords
  * 3) Identifying individuals
  * 4) E-mail magazine distribution
  * 5) Site login authentication
  * 6) Dispatch of mail and others
  * 7) Disclosure of information for communication between the parties in the case of a breach of rules or contract
  * 8) Information about new services
  * 9) Information about campaigns and questionnaires
  * 10) Inquiries about the Company or its services
  * 11) Payment of compensation
  * 12) Ad distribution during login

##### 11\. APP developer information (Applis Market)

Disclosed

To be used for the following services:

  * 1) Sending information materials by e-mail
  * 2) Reporting and communicating review results, etc.
  * 3) Reissuing passwords
  * 4) Identifying individuals
  * 5) E-mail magazine distribution
  * 6) Control screen log-in authentication
  * 7) Indicating company profile, services, results and seminar information to users
  * 8) Disclosure of information for communication between the parties in the case of a breach of rules or contract

##### 12\. Gift Smart

Disclosed

To be used for the following services:

  * 1) Reporting and communicating review results, etc.
  * 2) Identifying individuals
  * 3) Identifying bank account information
  * 4) Disclosure of information for communication between the parties in the case of a breach of rules or contract
  * 5) Reissuing passwords
  * 6) Responses to inquiries
  * 7) E-mail magazine distribution
  * 8) Information about campaigns and questionnaires
  * 9) Information about new services
  * 10) Sending information materials by e-mail or through the post
  * 11) Delivery of gifts (provide recipient shipping addresses to gift sellers)

##### 13\. Advertiser information (ADPRESSO)

Disclosed

To be used for the following services:

  * 1) Sending materials by e-mail, etc.
  * 2) Telephone communication concerning requests for sales visits, etc.
  * 3) Sales visits *around the time of prior review, depending on the circumstances
  * 4) Responses to inquiries (e-mail, telephone)
  * 5) Identifying individuals
  * 6) Prior review
  * 7) Reporting and communicating prior review results, etc.
  * 8) Control screen log-in authentication
  * 9) Reissuing passwords
  * 10) E-mail magazine distribution
  * 11) Information about campaigns and questionnaires
  * 12) Disclosure of information for communication between the parties in the case of a breach of rules or contract
  * 13) Indicating the name of application, URL, contents and name of person in charge of contract (company name in the case of company registration) to publishers

##### 14\. Publisher information (ADPRESSO)

Disclosed

To be used for the following services:

  * 1) Sending materials by e-mail, etc.
  * 2) Telephone communication concerning requests for sales visits, etc.
  * 3) Sales visits *around the time of prior review, depending on the circumstances
  * 4) Responses to inquiries (e-mail, telephone)
  * 5) Identifying individuals
  * 6) Review
  * 7) Reporting and communicating review results, etc.
  * 8) Control screen log-in authentication
  * 9) Reissuing passwords
  * 10) E-mail magazine distribution
  * 11) Information about campaigns and questionnaires
  * 12) Disclosure of information for communication between the parties in the case of a breach of rules or contract
  * 13) Payment of compensation
  * 14) Indicating the name of publishers, URL, contents and name of person in charge of contract (company name in the case of company registration) to advertisers

#### 3\. Matters concerning procedures responding to the requests for the notification or disclosure of the purpose of use of “personal information subject to the disclosure,” correction, addition or deletion of content, the suspension of its use, erasure, and the suspension of its provision to third parties (hereinafter, “Disclosure, etc.”)

##### ・Specifying the personal information held by the person subject to the request for Disclosure, etc.

Personal information subject to disclosure will mean personal information held where the Company has the authorization to respond to requests for the disclosure, correction, addition or deletion of content, the suspension of its use, erasure and the suspension of its provision to third parties, in which the Company may respond fully to the request made by the said individual.

##### ・Method of requesting Disclosure, etc.

Please contact the inquiry section for matters concerning the protection of personal information for requests concerning Disclosure, etc. Please note in advance that we will confirm the identification of the individual.

#### 4\. User web-browsing behavior information

The Company provides Behavioral Targeting Advertisements, based on the information that is collected and stored in relation to the web-browsing behavior of customers (or end-users) visiting an advertiser’s website (or web application) that uses ADPRESSO.

##### ・Information of user behavior history, which is collected 

Included are records on the web page viewing of an advertiser’s website (or web application), click history for advertisements distributed by ADPRESSO, ads displaying history, and product purchase history. This information cannot lead to the identification of specific individuals. The information collected online is retained for up to two years.

##### ・Purpose of use

To provide Behavioral Targeting Advertisements (including services to personalize advertising for content viewed by customers based on the personal attributes of customers, such as hobbies and interests) to advertiser companies that use ADPRESSO.

##### ・Disabling Behavioral Targeting Advertisements

If customers do not wish to see ads from Behavioral Targeting Advertisements, they can suspend the displays that the Company provides by disabling the advertising displays.

#### 5\. Inquiry section

Personal Information Protection Administrator,  
ValueCommerce Co., Ltd.  
Ark Hills South Tower  
1-4-5 Roppongi, Minato-ku, Tokyo
